efulfillmentservice.com 2009-06-22

# PRIVACY POLICY - PRODUCT FULFILLMENT COMPANY | FULFILLMENTSERVICES.COM

Your security and right to privacy are important to us. Please take a moment to review our privacy policy. Feel free to email our [Sales Department](http://www.efulfillmentservice.com/index.php/contact/d.sales/) or call us between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m., E.S.T., at 1-866-922-6783 with any questions or concerns. 

## Visitors

We do not currently collect individually-identifiable information from our web site visitors, except when soliciting them as clients on our “sign up” page. In the future, we may decide to improve our site's ability to obtain information about users. We will update this privacy statement to ensure that you are aware of developments in this area. 

## Clients

When you sign up for services using our online registration form, your company information is stored on our secure server. We hold and review your registration application in order to reply to your questions and set-up your account. Once the registration process is complete, you will access your password-protected account via our limited-access client login page. 

Email Notifications  
EFS reserves the right to communicate with clients via email in the following situations: 

  * Notify of additions to or changes in service, fees or regulations
  * Respond to email inquiries
  * Confirm orders, payments and registrations placed online
  * Send information that a customer has requested, such as tracking information and confirmation of orders
  * Provide emergency, security and online account maintenance information

eFulfillment Service supports and complies with all laws governing its email communications and will update this policy as needed to ensure ongoing compliance. 

## Third Parties

When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We do not share, sell, rent or disclose information obtained online about our visitors or clients to anyone outside of EFS. The only exceptions to this rule are the following: 

  * You specifically authorize EFS to share your information with another company,
  * Disclosure is required by law or we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site,
  * Disclosure is necessary to protect the safety of clients, and EFS partners or employees,
  * We share data with our authorized EFS partners, only to the extent necessary for them to perform a service for you.

Our site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
